question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States "
                 "if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'Ananas' is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Di-hydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 "
                 "inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vietnam national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
